# Yuhan Pan

Tel: 672-338-8355 | Email: alessiopangamer@gmail.com | GitHub: github.com/maize1111

### SUMMARY

Over 4 years of work experience in DevOps Engineering and System Automation

Over 2 years of work experience in Full-Stack Development

Programming Languages: Java, Python, C/C++, JavaScript, SQL, HTML/CSS

Frameworks: Spring MVC, Spring Boot, FastAPI, MyBatis, Node.js, Vue.js, React

DevOps & Automation Tools: Git, Docker, Kubernetes, Prometheus, Kibana, Nginx, Tomcat, zabbix, shell, Pinpoint

Databases & Message Systems: MySQL, Oracle, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis, Elasticsearch, NATS, Kafka

Operating Systems: Linux (RedHat, CentOS, Ubuntu), Windows Server

### **EDUCATION**

# New York Institute of Technology, Vancouver Campus

Sep. 2023 – Dec. 2024

Master of Science, Cybersecurity

• Teaching Assistant for two classes: Intrusion Detection and Hacker Exploits; Advanced Network Security

### Shanghai University, China

Sep. 2014 – June 2018

B.S in Computer Science and Technology

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# China Life Insurance Company Ltd. – Data Center (Shanghai, China) System and DevOps Engineer, Project Manager

July 2018 – Aug. 2022

June 2020 - Aug. 2022

- Project Manager of 4 primary business systems of China Life Insurance Company, including the company's internal Instant Messaging System, the Digital Seal System, the Digital Signature System, and the Enterprise System Monitoring System (Based on Pinpoint) with the highest system peak daily transaction volume reaching 350,000
- DevOps Engineer and System Administrator of the 4 systems mentioned above. Mainly responsible for the daily operation and maintenance of the systems, including system security, deployment, upgrades, vulnerability remediation, customer IT support, and production fault handling
- Managed cross-functional teams within the department, including development and testing groups, driving continuous improvement of system features and addressing security vulnerabilities.
- Accomplished the end-to-end development process of the company's internal instant messaging system, from demand analysis to successful production launch, achieving a user base of 300,000 with 100,000 daily active users
- Pioneered the migration of the managed system's database from Oracle to PostgreSQL, achieving the company's annual target and becoming the first system within the organization to complete this migration
- Relevant Certificates: System Integration Project Management Engineer (China, Mid-Level) EXIN DevOps Foundation Certificate

#### Full-Stack Web Developer and DevOps Engineer

July 2018 - June 2020

- Collaborated in the design and development of a front-end **Vue.js** and back-end **Spring MVC** separated architecture for a Batch Job Management Platform (BMP) to monitor batch jobs, alert administrators, visualize business data for the company's primary business systems, integrating over a dozen systems
- Led continuous enhancement and iteration of features for the Data Quality Management Platform (Spring Boot)
- Implemented hierarchical and decentralized permission authentication and management for different user groups
- Developed and maintained a Kafka consumer program to process and analyze data from integrated systems
- Awarded the Innovation Star Award within the company for the BMP project's success
- DevOps engineer for the Insurance Underwriting Application including daily operations, maintaining system availability and stability, monitoring system and resolving issues

## Projects

### Relation Service System with NATS and FastAPI | Python, NATS, FastAPI

Sep. 2024 – Dec. 2024

- Building a newly human relation service system using NATS, and FastAPI, collaborated with Archethought
- Implementing hierarchical access management for Roles, and Users, with features like safety alerts, chat, messaging, and role-based access control for permissions management based on NATS using JWT and Singing Keys.

### Metal Surface Crack Detection $\mid C++, OpenCV, Qt \mid$

Feb. 2018 – June 2018

- Developed a crack detection tool using C++, OpenCV, and Qt
- Automated crack detection on metal surfaces and visualized results with a GUI interface